Sherilyn A. Moline

Tampa, Florida ◆ Phone (813) 786-0525

E-mail: smoline@gmail.com Portfolio: http://SherilynMoline.me Github: https://github.com/smoline + Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/smoline/

WEB APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

Team oriented, quality minded, and motivated Ruby on Rails Developer with a solid record of accomplishments emphasizing training and development management in a highly competitive, rapidly growing industry. Demonstrated leadership, problem solving, and planning skills resulting in an integrated system of creative, timely, and practical programs.

Additional strengths:

Ruby on Rails HTML Problem Solving
Erb CSS Communicating
MVC Sass Team Building
Agile Development JavaScript Researching
SQL jQuery Troubleshooting

Postgresql Test Driven Development Training

PROFESSIONAL ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Worked in a Team of Ruby on Rails Developers. Using github the team created a silent auction web application using Rails 5.0, Ruby 2.4, bcrypt, OmniAuth, and Shrine. Using Agile Development we delivered a mvp with time to spare. **Result:** Delivered a customizable web application that could be used at any number of Fundraising Galas. The client was pleased.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Ruby on Rails Program Graduate, The Iron Yard

March 2017 - June 2017

 Attended 12-week intensive back-end engineering course designed to give the students the tools and experience needed to enter a career as a junior web applications developer

President, Moline Services, Inc.

January 2011 - Present

- Business support company providing professional services on a contract basis to small businesses and sole practitioner law firms.
- Including administrative support, office management, professional photography, and computer and network support.

Living in Germany

August 2009 - January 2011

Office Manager, West Coast Family Practice

April 2007 - August 2009

Provided administrative support to the owner of the practice, including creating procedures
for new web based insurance pre-authorizations, and eligibility checks. Researched the new
market of EMR software for our practice upgrade. Familiar with CollaborateMD and Practice
Fusion software solutions.

President, ProTechConnect, Inc.

April 2005 - April 2007

• Computer support company providing business and home technical computer hardware and software support.

EDUCATION / TRAINING / CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Science Degree in Management Information Systems University of South Florida

Tampa, FL - 2008

Ruby on Rails Program Graduate, The Iron Yard

St.Petersburg, FL - 2017